const dayFifteenQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who was nicknamed “Living Martyr” by The Prophet?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Sa’du bn Mu’adh",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "Hanzalah bn Abi ‘Aamir",
      "Talhah bn ‘Ubaydullah",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Who died last among the companions of the Prophet?",
    options: [
      "Ka’b bn Malik",
      "At Tufayl bn ‘Amri Ad Dusiy",
      "Bilal bn Robah",
      "Hilal bn Umayyah",
      "Abu Tufayl ‘Aamir bn Waathlah Allaythiy",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the companion known as Dhu Nuur?",
    options: [
      "Ka’b bn Malik",
      "At Tufayl bn ‘Amri Ad Dusiy",
      "Bilal bn Robah",
      "Hilal bn Umayyah",
      "Abu Tufayl ‘Aamir bn Waathlah Allaythiy",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the blind Adhan during the lifetime of the Prophet?",
    options: [
      "Ka’b bn Malik",
      "‘Abdullah bn Umm Makktum",
      "Bilal bn Robah",
      "Hilal bn Umayyah",
      "Marwan bn Rabi’",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where did Bilal bn Rabah (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion, die?",
    options: ["Madinah", "Iraq", "Yemen", "Damascus", "Egypt"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the companion whose eye protruded during the battle of Badr and Prophet returned it to the normal place?",
    options: [
      "Qatadah bn Nu’man",
      "Usamah bn Zayd",
      "Talhah bn ‘Ubaydullah",
      "Zubayr bn ‘Awam",
      "Hakim bn Hizam",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which ‘Abdu (slave) among the ‘Abeed (slaves) that first accepted Islam?",
    options: [
      "Qatadah bn Nu’man",
      "Usamah bn Zayd",
      "Talhah bn ‘Ubaydullah",
      "Zubayr bn ‘Awam",
      "Bilal bn Rabah",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "What is the name of the first Masjid (mosque) built in Islam?",
    options: [
      "Masjid Unaizah",
      "Masjid Qubah",
      "Masjid Quraish",
      "Masjid Sham",
      "Masjid Arqam",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) said “Every Prophet has disciples and disciple of this nation is ……………………..",
    options: [
      "Qatadah bn Nu’man",
      "Usamah bn Zayd",
      "Talhah bn ‘Ubaydullah",
      "Zubayr bn ‘Awam",
      "Hakim bn Hizam",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many years was the tenure of Abubakar Siddiq (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "4 years and 3 months",
      "2 years and 9 months",
      "4 years and 9 months",
      "2 years and 3 months",
      "3 years and 2 months",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Two Sahabah (Companions) were 60 years old before accepting Islam, both lived for 60 years after accepting Islam and both died in Madinah in the year 54 AH, they are ………….and…………..",
    options: [
      "Bilal bn Rabah and ‘Abdullahi bn ‘Abbas",
      "Bilal bn Rabah and Anas bn Malik",
      "Hakim bn Hizam and Hassaan bn Thaabith",
      "Talhah bn ‘Ubaydullah and Zubayr bn ‘Awam",
      "Qatadah bn Nu’man and Hakim bn Hizam",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "When was Sulhu Huddaibiyah?",
    options: [
      "6th year of Hijrah",
      "7th year of Hijrah",
      "8th year of Hijrah",
      "9th year of Hijrah",
      "10th year of Hijrah",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Who was the companion of the Prophet described as Ameenul Ummah (trustworthy of this nation)?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "Abu ‘Ubaidah ‘Aamir bn Jarah",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the companion that the prophet permitted to stay with his mother, due to her sickness, during the battle of Badr?",
    options: [
      "Uthman bn ‘Affan",
      "Abu ‘Ubaidah ‘Aamir bn Jarah",
      "Abu Qatadah Harithu bn Rib’y Al Ansari",
      "Hassaan bn Thaabith",
      "Abu Ummamah Albahiliy Sudayyu bn ‘Ajlan",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },

  {
    question:
      "What is the real name of Abu Sa’eed-l-Khudiry (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "Zaydu bn Harithah",
      "Hassaan bn Thaabith",
      "‘Aamir bn Jarah",
      "Sa’du bn Maliki bn Sinan",
      "Abu Ummamah Albahiliy Sudayyu bn ‘Ajlan",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
];

export default dayFifteenQuestions;
